Wise Man Daniel walks in the Spirit in Christ Jesus,
ministering Spirit-filled prayer in the power of the Holy Ghost.
Instantly, Jesus Christ is brought to the scene
and the spiritual entities that are causing crisis in the lives of the people are exposed
by the lightening from Heaven.
As Wise Man Daniel continued pouring light all over the congregants,
he encounters this young man who immediately falls under the power of deliverance
and the spiritual entity possessing his body is put in a very hot furnace.
The evil spirit refuses to confess.
So Wise Man Daniel continues to turn the heat up,
commanding Holy Ghost fire to descend upon him
and the unclean spirit is forced to talk.
Let's watch what happens next.
Come here!
Who are you?
I am not going to tell you.
Speak out!
Why do you want to know?
What have you done to him?
I have destroyed him. I gave him the spirit of lust.
I gave him destruction.
I'm going to ruin him until I kill him.
What is your mission?
To destroy him.
In what way?
I will make him lose concentration in anything he does.
What else have you done?
I gave him the spirit of lust.
What else?
I will make him bring more people for me.
What caliber of people do you want him to bring to you?
Youth.
What have you done to the youth?
I will destroy them.
How do you destroy them? Speak!
I destroy their future.
In what way?
I will make them lose concentration,
I will destroy them,
give them the spirit of lust.
How do you get these youth?
School area, everywhere.
When you go to school, how do you get the youth? Explain.
I will make friends with them and whatever I give them, that's all.
What do you normally give them?
I give them money,
I give them food
When you give them those things, what will happen to them?
They come with me.
Do you say anything before giving to them, or how do they follow you?
I just give to them.
And when they sleep, they come to me in my room.
Yes, I possess them.
How many youth have you succeeded in possessing?
Many!
How many?
Many, I can't count.
Is it boys and girls or boys alone?
Both boys and girls.
How do you get girls?
I sleep with them. I possess them.
In the night they become mine.
They become yours?
Yes.
When they become yours, what will then happen to them and their family?
When I possess them, they destroy their family members.
They act as a tool for me and my kingdom.
They posses everyone -
their siblings, brothers, sisters, everybody they know.
Is it secondary school you go to or university?
Secondary schools and primary schools.
You have initiated many?
Yes, but most especially in secondary schools.
How many, can you just give a number of how many you have initiated?
I have lost count, there are so many.
They are so many?
Yes.
How did you enter his body?
He caught my fish; my golden fish.
How did he catch the fish?
He was passing and he saw some people catching fish.
He joined them and unfortunately he took my precious fish.
Did he eat the fish?
No, he took it home.
What happened when he took it home?
He wanted to use the fish,
but a spirit asked him to take the fish away.
I heard them saying that.
But before they came for the fish, I entered him.
The fish was no more.
They looked for the fish but they could not find it
because I had already entered him.
Who are you?
I am the king of kings.
Of the evil kingdom?
Yes, I posses all the youth.
You possess all the youths?
Yes, that is my specialty.
That is your specialty?
Yes.
On this earth?
Now, you said that he caught your golden fish; your precious fish.
Does it mean you live inside the water?
Yes.
What is your position in the water?
I am the king.
You are the king?
Yes.
How do you operate in the water?
I send my fish out and if you get them,
if you eat them, you become a tool.
I would use you as I want.
Do you stay in the ocean or a river?
All the streams.
You are everywhere?
Yes.
What have you done to his family?
I have destroyed all his family members.
In what way? How have you destroyed them?
No one goes beyond secondary school level.
What level has he attended?
He just finished his SSCE.
No one goes beyond secondary school level in his family?
Yes, in all his extended family, no one succeeds.
No one! Not even one!
Not even one?
Yes!
Why did you allow him to come here?
He has been watching Emmanuel TV and he was arrested.
As much as I tried to stop him, I couldn't.
He was arrested through Emmanuel TV?
Yes.
Were you sleeping when he came here today?
No.
Where were you?
I was in him, but I couldn't stop him
because the pressure to come here was too much.
He had the zeal to come here, I couldn't stop him.
Fire all over your body!
Fire!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Holy Ghost fire!
All over your body!
From your head to your toe!
All over!
Come here!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Let me practice and I will deal with you!
Okay, practice.
I will deal with you!
A demonic king, from the evil kingdom based in the water
has completely manifested itself through the boy
and is now provoked to challenge the wise man.
He asked the wise man for some time to practise his moves
and begins dancing and skipping, using the faculties of the boy to warm up
in preparation to physically attack the wise man.
Are you ready?
Let's go!
Holy Ghost fire!
Fire all over your body!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Do you want to practise?
Okay, practise.
Last bus stop!
Wise Man Daniel gives the boy more time to practise
and the boy continues practising and warming up once again for a second round.
Are you okay now?
Let's go again.
Okay, come closer - the gap is too much, come closer.
I will deal with you.
Fire!
All over your body!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Do you want to practise more?
Yes!
Okay, practise.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Two rounds have passed with Wise Man Daniel clearly having the upper hand
and the demonic king continues using the faculties of the boy to do more extensive training.
A few more arm pushouts in different directions is the new power exercise.
Are you okay now?
Okay.
If you have power, pass this line.
Draw it. Draw it very well.
He draws out the battlefield line between him and the wise man,
stretching his right leg way out and sketching it on the ground.
He then stamps it with his hand before giving it the final touch.
Pass this line.
I should pass that line?
Pass the line.
Okay.
Oh God, if you come near me!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
You are still coming?
Fire!
Fire all over your body!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
The battle is over with a fiery knockout blow.
In Jesus' name.
Thank You, Lord. You are delivered. Rise up.
Set free In Jesus' Name
Come here.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Who is the owner of this pair of shoes?
These are my shoes.
How come they are off from your feet?
I don't know.
But you were putting them on before?
Yes, and I was standing over there.
Now, how come they are here?
Did you remove my shoes?
It's not me.
You don't know who removed them?
No.
You said you are the king of kings?
Which kingdom?
You are asking me which kingdom?
Because I don't know, I am not a king.
You said you are the king of kings from the evil kingdom.
I'm not even a king how could I be king of kings?
From the evil kingdom.
No.
You said you go about possessing the youth all over the world.
You specialise in possessing the youth in the secondary schools.
No, I didn't say so.
You initiate them through food, biscuits, items.
You give items to them, they meet you through dreams in your kingdom.
No.
You said you have initiated thousands of youth.
I have many friends, but I don't initiate people.
You wanted to fight me here.
Me? How can I fight you?
You don't know you wanted to fight me?
No, where is the power?
Fight you like this? I did not fight you.
How come you are sweating like this?
I don't know. Is the A/C not on?
I saw you, you were taking water and pouring it on your body.
What was happening to you that time?
You took it three times and were pouring it on your body - three consecutive times.
What was happening to you?
Actually, when I came here, after some time, I started feeling heat on me.
I was no longer comfortable.
But I never knew I poured water on myself.
You poured water on youself three times.
What was happening to you when you were pouring this water on yourself?
I was hot. There was fire all over my body.
Were you able to quench it with this water?
I felt fire. But I didn't know that I took water from anywhere but I felt fire.
You didn't know you used this water on your body?
No.
You are free.
Thank You, Jesus!
I'm delivered! Thank You, Jesus
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.
TT:Lizz Ndung'u 10/11/2017
RV: Jacqueline Fernandez 07/02/18 + Mel